const dayTwentyOneQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "Is Solatu Janazah allowed after burying the corpse for those who missed the Salat before burying?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Is a husband allowed to wash his wife’s corpse (Ghuslu Janazah)?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Salat is the first that Prophet Muhammad (May the peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him) prayed out of 5 daily prayers?",
    options: [
      "Salatu ‘Ishai",
      "Salatul Magrib",
      "Salatul ‘Asr",
      "Salatuz Zuhur",
      "Salatul Fajr",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Is it allowed for a child from Zina (illegal sexual Intercourse) to be Imam or lead us in Prayer?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Is it right to fast on the second of Shawwal (a day after Eid al-Fitr)?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the companion named Faarisu rosulillah (Equestrian of messenger of Allah)?",
    options: [
      "Uthman bn ‘Affan",
      "Abu ‘Ubaidah ‘Aamir bn Jarah",
      "Abu Qatadah Harithu bn Rib’y Al Ansari",
      "Hassaan bn Thaabith",
      "Abu Ummamah Albahiliy Sudayyu bn ‘Ajlan",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Hassan Basari (May the blessings of Allaah be upon him) is among the ………",
    options: [
      "Messengers",
      "Prophets",
      "Companions",
      "Successors",
      "Successors of Successors",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Mawlah (loyalist) among the Mawaliy (loyalists) first accepted Islam?",
    options: [
      "Zaydu bn Harithah",
      "Hassaan bn Thaabith",
      "‘Aamir bn Jarah",
      "Sa’du bn Maliki bn Sinan",
      "Abu Ummamah Albahiliy Sudayyu bn 'Ajlan",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Sa’eed bn Musayyib (May Blessings of Allaah be upon him) is among the ………",
    options: [
      "Messengers",
      "Prophets",
      "Companions",
      "Successors",
      "Successors of Successors",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the child that first accepted Islam?",
    options: [
      "Ali bn Abi Talib",
      "‘Abdullah bn ‘Abbas",
      "‘Abdullahi bn Umar",
      "‘Ammar bn Yasir",
      "Mus’ab bn ‘Umayr",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the King that reached the setting place of the sun and rising place of the sun, mentioned in Suratul Khaf?",
    options: ["Luqman", "Dhulqarnayn", "Hadir", "Sabah", "Sulaiman"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "No newborn baby spoke from the cradle except three. Among them is ………",
    options: [
      "Companion of Jurayj",
      "Prophet Yusuf",
      "Junaid",
      "Prophet Musa",
      "Maryam bint ‘Imran",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the real name of Abu Lahb (uncle of Prophet Muhammad)?",
    options: [
      "‘Abdullah bn ‘Abdil Mutalib",
      "‘Uzza bn ‘Abdil Mutalib",
      "‘Abdul Manaf bn ‘Abdil Mutalib",
      "Hashim bn ‘Abdil Mutalib",
      "‘Abdul ‘Uzza bn ‘Abdil Mutalib",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Abu Lahb’s wife?",
    options: [
      "Layth bint Harib bn Umayyah",
      "Arwah bint Ubal bn Umayyah",
      "Layth bint Ubal bn Umayyah",
      "Arwah bint Harib bn Umayyah",
      "Khaalatu bint Harib bn Umayyah",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Who first started Qasaamah (rule of distribution) among Arab?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Isma’eel",
      "‘Abdul Mutalib",
      "‘Amru bn ‘Aamir bn Luhayi Al Khuza’iy",
      "Kilab",
      "Qusah",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
];

export default dayTwentyOneQuestions;
